const questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: 'Who Is The Top Goal-Scorer Of Champions League ?',
        answer: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
        options: [
            'Lionel Messi',
            'Cristiano Ronaldo',
            'Pele',
            'Diego Maradona'
        ],
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: 'Which Team Is Famous For Their PlayStyle Known As Tiki-Taka',
        answer: 'Barcelona',
        options: [
            'Real Madrid',
            'Valencia',
            'Sevilla',
            'Barcelona'
        ],
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: 'Which Manager Has Won The Most Premier League Trophies ?',
        answer: 'Sir Alex Ferguson',
        options: [
            'Pep Guardiola',
            'Jose Mourinho',
            'Sir Alex Ferguson',
            'Carlos Ancelotti'
        ],
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: 'Which Player Has Scored The Most Goals In a Calender Year ?',
        answer: 'Lionel Messi',
        options: [
            'Cristiano Ronaldo',
            'Ronaldinho',
            'Lionel Messi',
            'Robert Lewandowski'
        ],
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: 'Which Teams Has Won The Most Number Of Champions League Title ?',
        answer: 'Real Madrid',
        options: [
            'Bayern Munchen',
            'Real Madrid',
            'Barcelona',
            'Liverpool'
        ],
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: 'Pichichi Trophy Is Awarded To The Player Who Scored Most Goal In A Season Of Which League ?',
        answer: 'La Liga',
        options: [
            'La Liga',
            'Bundesliga',
            'Premier League',
            'Seria A'
        ],
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: 'Who Is The Only Manager To Win The League Title Of All Top 5 Leagues ?',
        answer: 'Carlos Ancelotti',
        options: [
            'Pep Guardiola',
            'Jose Mourinho',
            'None',
            'Carlos Ancelotti'
        ],
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: '"La Pulga" Is The Nick Name Of Which Player ?',
        answer: 'Lionel Messi',
        options: [
            'Lionel Messi',
            'David Villa',
            'Luka Modric',
            'Cesc Fabregas'
        ],
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: 'Apart From Barcelona Which Is The Only Other Team To Win Sextuple ?',
        answer: 'Bayern Munchen',
        options: [
            'Liverpool',
            'Real Madrid',
            'Bayern Munchen',
            'Juventus'
        ],
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: 'Which Player Has The Most Goal Contributions After Messi & Ronaldo ?',
        answer: 'Luis Suarez',
        options: [
            'Zlatan Ibrahimovic',
            'Luis Suarez',
            'Neymar Jr',
            'Robert Lewandowski'
        ],
    },
]